Here, medically speaking, get ready to
meditate.
First details, clear. Yesterday we had
a good class with all the
volunteers.
[Music] There
are 200 volunteers who are working very hard on this.
I would like to thank them. [
Applause]
[Music]
[Applause]
What was the topic yesterday? I've already
forgotten. Last night we talked about something
impossible. I find it impossible. If you have an argument with your husband in the
kitchen, then this man
is a password.
The pen comes from me because I have a
seed in my mind. Advantage for
the pen and doesn't have it, that's why
a dog is together. Makes you a
dog or a human. Okay, I have
really together in my mind.
We had the pen ladies together. The
team idea. Only you can do this.
You can know another person,
but giving is impossible. How can you give the
seed? Pen collector. The one who
gives must
give someone else a pen, and when you see that your hand
opens, then that gives a collection
in your guests. Now
yesterday we had three questions in the
heart. Here to 3rd grade
and my friends.
I would have here now  The pole position.
I asked three questions.
Here, the other person knows. You are
not allowed to answer.
Other people, three questions: Do I have a
pen in my hand? Yes. There isn't one in
my hand. Yes. Is there a pen in
my hand that comes from me? Yes, because
I don't have a pen.
Now comes a difficult question. The one
from the foundation is called this. That's why. Therefore,
the person who has learned the
ropes really understands. They love to give
things to other people. That's a
sign that this person
understands. They are polite to everyone. They
smile at someone. They give other people
things because they have nothing to understand.
This morning we will do the life dance
meditation.
I spoke with Alter and Dreher.
They told me how far they have come in
the meditation.
And we will go even further today. We
will do the eight-step tour.
When the elevator goes up, and then
we go to the ninth floor. We will
meditate there above us. A
teacher is any teacher
in their life. It would be your first
teacher in elementary school. Because the
mother from a kindergarten party belongs to
the mother and the father.  Then you have a
school year, you have a teacher here at work,
then you have your wife's teacher, later you
have the children's teacher, maybe
you now have a spiritual teacher, but in
this meditation,
if we ask three questions, number one, is there a
teacher in your guest? Number
two, is there
an empty spirit from your group?
Come together, yes, now 3, is there a
teaching in one guest? Doesn't come together from all of them?
And no, impossible. This
message to the teacher, do
you want to awaken these people?
[Music]
There is no teacher who doesn't collect from euros.
He has, do you understand, do you give to
other people?
Whoever doesn't understand, will you give
nothing to other people? If you learn,
understand, then you respect your
teacher who comes from you. If you don't
understand, then you don't respect the teacher,
and then you don't make any seeds for
the teacher, and then the
teacher disappears. Something in this direction,
Stifter Realschule, work, taught
all these teachers, we will the right of
their and the witnesses, thereby new  seeds
then the teacher stays with us that the
beginning makes noises we meditate
in a group therefore pay special
attention that seeks to be back
strive to exist
we will meditate a little longer today
make yourselves comfortable
normally in meditation
we begin by observing our breathing
but here we begin by
observing the air conditioner
therefore a mind on the sound of the
air conditioner don't forget the special kind of
technique in meditation when you
exhale the end of the breath
then exhale a little more air
then you will not become restless during the meditation will
have the air conditioner
[Music]
there might be another one
coming then please to the heart the
uppermost the heartbeat is not in the
had we are not yet in the heart inside
will observe the heartbeat
we have time
which now into the heart the heart
beats around us its behavior had heart
inside it is not dark
and wet is the beautiful room lots of
sunlight
with
I remember I remember I remember you
there were the additional exhale
tradition
yao garden gate
now we go into the center of the heart
and the  The heartbeat feels very far away.
Let's place a mind now into the individual
crystals. From the outside, it
looks much smaller, but when we
bring the mind into the sugar crystals,
it's a very pleasant
meditation space with lots of
sunlight.
Now I make my mind too big for
the Pacific Ocean. The situation that I'm going
through this whole world, spanning the whole world.
Friedel, before myself,
I remind you to do the extra
exhalation.
Now we bring in the plan of heaven. The
mind carries itself from the ocean depths up to
the sky.
Now we seem to be turning off the mind, just like
here in turning off the light around the room.
If a thought comes up,
then block that thought
in the 66.
Remember the extra order.
Other things on the
left, mind,
thoughts, and images on the lists,
let that happen and let them disappear. Don't
wrestle or fight with the rest,
the dreary reality. Now we are
ready. Meditation begins
this month. Many ask for a teacher in
your life. Maybe it's a
mother or a father or your
school year and was then only in a
tuxedo, they said that they come
to you in a friendly, happy way, to
meditate with you.
They come to you,
she is very happy about it.
It is not an image that comes to you,
but it is a real improvement.
Breathing is better.
Click on yourself with a lot of love, a
big smile. When you meditate with a teacher, and
a teacher knows that this will help
urgently, a teacher to sit here.
The old station
is now
thinking about something in the quality of the teacher
that you really appreciate,
perhaps his ability to
remain patient and/or the ability
to help many others.
The teacher is again a pen.
The good thing that I see in my teacher here
comes from me. Maybe I made
one together for it.
If you think of the past life, the first
law of chambers, it perhaps says
that the seed is the same as the
result. If a teacher is very patient,
then I must have been very patient in my
past life. If my
teacher is very helpful to other opponents,
then I must have been very helpful in the
past life.
Let's go on a journey into our
past lives. Stop, and the
damp walls where  I lived
hundreds of years ago, what do you think
my work, my task,
about the one bankruptcy
here, I looked like, if man or
woman,
how far my family looked, what
he planned, you this beautiful
quality in my teacher, a lot of
hate in meditation, no limit
of size, free, I hope a
beautiful story, don't be
afraid to make a film out of it,
you are the good one, holds in this film and
civilians,
we are spending some time here now,
enjoy it, Sundays, are you distracted,
you think lunch is no
longer, then slowly come back to
meditation,
yes, contact us now, come back
to a year, get it again, enjoy
these beautiful qualities, if you, you
can, you ask in three questions,
Mainz, that with Tiffert, it has, my teacher,
the very beautiful quality,
with number two comes this beautiful
quality from me,
with 0, 3, that the player, colleague, came from the
net,
this beautiful, beautiful
quality comes from oneself, and the
answer is no, changes, that is empty,
holds,
if my teacher has empty, then I can
hold the teacher in my life,
if I already  Sharing from experience, when
I share with other people who are
interested, then
the seed plants itself. 27
Keeping my teachers by my side
as a compact thing,
that this is now going down together again.
The DTTTB wants to say respectfully to
his teacher that we will now go out for something from
meditation.
Welcome below to the eighth, where
thoughts formed, I noticed
it was super quiet.
The mind speaks, maybe, but I'm not too tired.
The defective witch, remember
to do the extra breathing.
Now I'm going to level number two, which is
the vehicles
in the community. Thoughts are sent and
I block them, and to keep them in mind
that they are in the sky.
Now I bring my mind back to
closer and to the sky,
which is now back only to the ocean, very deep,
international, is now very gentle in
the sugar crystals, tiny. Remember
the extra breathing.
Now to the cent, into the
heart center. The heartbeat has moved far away.
He has in his hair, from the now
into the interior of the heart. Now
walls are beating around me.
It comes back into the body and
observes a heart
in North Texas, the short legs, Robert,
now three long ones, endure the
meditation, moreover, because
open,
when opening, and stretches,
replays, the file towers are now at the place,
because finding the easy ways
is DSDS, he was, receives a new principle,
that is called once again length points, the way
he speaks in China
has the exit,
military spokesman, they teach me
Chinese, I say to my
Chinese friends, not like that,
they look at me so strangely,
he puts the chip system in, she does it the
same way
[Music],
we get a body and a guide
to lands at the airport, and then you go
to rental cars, then you pay and
get a car, huge cheers, and that's exactly how it became,
the countries,
you would get a rental car,
why didn't I tell you to
buy a car, because you have to give it back
if you didn't have the money for it, you have to, moreover,
if you, it is time,
this body, this body, you only have
temporarily, applied at the moment to the body, or it
was too hot, is
the cabaret hungry, I  I have a
friend who said she'll never
eat meat like an animal, and all
her friends ate fish, and
when she was hungry, she ate fish
too. She eventually decided to become a
vegetarian, but
because she was very, very hungry and there was no
other food, she ended up
eating with her fingers.
So, if you're in this car, then
you'll do bad things to take care of yourself, and this
is a car to take care of,
but that doesn't mean it's not a good
car.
This car needs to be started 23 times and thanked for it.
This car needed sweaters. This
car needs many things. Of course,
everyone here in the room is a nice person. Emergency
call, the rating here, nobody here
would stand for the workflow in the world
with funny people. There are
few places in this world where
500 people are together, young
media, and you can leave your wallet
and nobody will
take it, although that's because everyone here
is Buddhist.
But if they really need money,
their mother is the same, or the
children are starving,
then they would probably take it.
Everyone would take it, I
probably would too, and we're the same.
We have this rental car,
we try then  To be a good person
and not hurt others,
but if we had nothing to eat here,
we would stand. That's how
people are;
we would steal to feed this body.
Because from the discount store Colmex, and in the
next life we'll get another one.
But this car belonged to the same
person. It's
not a Tesla, you can see that it
's an old American car
that breaks down all the time. It
needs a sweater and it needs something
to eat.
It needs it. It does so many things, has to
go to the toilet.
It's not a good car.
Inside, there's only blood, flesh,
and bones.
Since there
are 5000 important components of a
clown in the populations of Berlin, and they don't work well
together,
the lungs fight with the heart. When
we move, the lungs and heart want to stay cooler, want to go
to the moon, and the heart
needs more warmth. When we
fight hard, they fight
each other, and when the lungs win,
Rico Sander says to us, it's cold. When the heart is
warmed,
then we have problems breathing. It comes
from the devil, complete quality, and the
5000 parts that fight
each other, that compete with each other.
I studied
safer use for several years for a traditional doctor, and
he said something very interesting:
if the lungs and heart are in balance, that
's a hooray! It's totally unusual for
a healthy person to be normal.
For me, a
sick person is normal.
Health is only temporary. To
get food, even
good people, if there was
nothing to eat here in the hotel, that only
wings have to, then we would
stand for food to stay alive.
In war, everyone does bad things,
and if we die, like the consumer
Thuringia found, because we stole food, certainly,
then we get a body like this in a way that
can be
considered lucky because it's with
cash,
but it's not particularly good. Why did
Bayer do bad things to
get this body,
and now we have this body.
We have to eat,
we have to work, and if we don't get
food, we stand for it. And
if you play, destroy markets,
then next time you get
the same kind of body again, a body hardened by
stealing and stealing.  To represent,
this is also a cycle,
this is Sarah, this is a curse, and this is
proof that you are in St.
So we have to leave this chamber behind us,
we have to change it,
and if the teachers are direct and fair
from the beginning, then from the inside,
the body will change from the inside out, you will
see the body change, and
then you will never again possess such a body,
tourists, a better body,
a body length, a wonder body,
he doesn't need food anymore, and he would
never hurt a person to
get food, and the body consists,
that's totally awesome, but he is really
cool, if you are in hate, youth Huber,
Minister of the Interior,
then you can help many people at the same time
in many cities, you
have a very efficient body, perceive it,
it is a real Tesla model, and then
it is not rented but suddenly
permanent, never had to give it back, at the
moment it is in my whole body,
and that's what we have to change, we have to
change it, and don't wait until it's time to go
to the airport to learn, do it while
the youth fire brigade is experiencing, the
teachers, the work, and all the other
things in your life,
these are not  Emergencies, but
changing the body is super important, we have to do it,
and the best way
to do it is to
spend so much time with
the majority.
I know she needs a toilet break,
which will be explained a little
further in the text.
I'm going to come to the one who
knows because this body was
created from bad seeds,
we will always have problems.
He will always be in the hospital,
he will always be hungry, always have to go
to the toilet.
That's not a good thing. Even
if you're not sick right now,
mediators in San Bruno,
maybe one is working inside you, I just don't know it yet.
Maybe we already have cancer and it's
not obvious yet. Fighting for gold,
we have a friend who recently got
cancer. I think she's dying
now, and we're all totally surprised. You
were still in class last
month,
you still look good. I didn't know
I had cancer. Regarding the end,
even if you're not feeling well right now, don't worry.
It's rather
bad for people,
that's the nature of the body. We have to tell
the media
because the  screen so this couple of
these was created by bad karma
and then we're in st
and now we're dealing with
these two days was until
this body is again pen that
the ladies want to support are the
same he also comes from Kenzo what does
this strange body do
two things one bad karma always
fits that in the past
maybe I
ate meat in my past lives
because of me these animals were killed
something very bad happened at the
moment
10 billion space are brought to China every year
[Music]
and each of these chickens
also has the body they want to live so
could be the turning point go to McDonald's
then it comes together and the
salad is not the same as a
human devil in st the
scientists have found
that there is poison in the meat what's it called
again
if you have too much fat in your blood you have
cholesterol
the main source of cholesterol is
meat and 65 of the Americans whose
meat and then they have cholesterol
in their blood
before deals and die every year
400,000 people because they go to McDonald's
and eat similar things
[Music]
it's with Green Racing, that keeps
me healthy.
I think I wanted to be a vegetarian 40 years ago.
Franz Thoma, Mr. Putin, and
my friends told me you'll want
him now. You were
sick,
you weren't healthy.
They've all died by now.
Understand, you don't need meat.
You need it. You're just causing
problems for others. So, touting
Scorsese bonuses. So, two things
cause this body. Karama quad
cores come. What causes came. Very
famous verse interpreter progress.
The finished chapter of the Abi da Marco
Schacht. Let's do it
together. The skillful one.
So, almost all the stars that you shoot in the
sky come from Caramba chemical
company. December. What is came? There is
raw chamber. Must take care of evil.
The most basic Karama. If you think
that is, any of us can make
many chambers now. It's so cold here.
I have to go to the toilet.
Why does he speak so slowly today? Takes
me with how come and we have
in 30 customers what made
linking is must Breivik could one
think is the most basic Artemis
chamber put warehouse in the bags
Berghammer and secondary came
[Music]
this body is caused by karma
what we say and what we do
and what we do and what we say
thereby our thinking of separate
brands before dry
the thought is a second before you
speak a second before we do something
think who only pink film
we think something it's too cold
I have to find out game music Germany
and then when you see that you the
commune then you make body came that get
finished
that is body chamber cinemas and then
you say something that they are finished but the
class is good you are doing well that glass
works co
this class is good for Eskimos
the Eskimos stand would the class be
liked
Finke comes before and the thinking comes
shortly before the transport to the first
thought and then or do something
camera is Jean King
the mother of karma is so if you
understand because it is the one who made this body
How we make this body,
how the doors of the film have to go,
we have to cover the cover, then to the party,
I am, I think we will deal with this in
the next two or three videos and deal with it, there
we deal with
karma, the thought of beating him up,
how can we improve it, wants to
bring E10 and then you change the
body, we make J  Now a break, note,
hour break,
move around a bit so they can see
for the team manager, and then we'll see each other again
in 15 minutes. Okay, as I
mentioned,
I think I've been teaching that lamps have been around for
eight years now, which
is already passé, and it's also good for you if you
learn a little bit about the content of the last few years. That's why
I'm repeating the content using
pictures.
Normally I do it in the evening,
but tonight we have
another task as bishop of [unclear]: we're going to
make a special fire, and
we also have three weddings.
What is the purpose of the fire? To me,
it has two meanings. The number one is that
we burn our old, worst
value in the feed.
We throw our old [unclear], came a
fire brigade, and that burns the old [unclear]
badly. If you've really done something really bad in your past,
and I think
all of us have, I think I've done that
too. If I were to tell you
everything I did in my
youth,
I think [unclear], write on a piece of
paper, end [unclear], and at the end of the
ceremony, live stream of [unclear], can you [unclear]  The
fire, then you can throw the paper into the
fire, and during the incident,
we have three fire pits. Some of the
experienced teachers,
some of them have also
done a three-year retreat. We have
several teachers who have completed the three-year
credit.
One of them is... because there isn't one like that at all,
and they help us with the fires.
You can also put things into the fire.
We will give you a plate,
and then you take it and throw it into the
fire. Don't do it so
elegantly, not so... You can
practice that now, and we will
help you. Good, there with style in the
corner. Think about it as a novel,
and then you have to
burn mentally. It will go worse.
That is the first meaning of
betrayal, and Buddhists love it when you...
bad, if one wanted to have... and
never be afraid of... your teacher felt
sick and had to tell the worst things from
his life.
They are happy that they are happy
that you are honest. Want to look for
climate goals, Utah mountains, and you
cleaned up together. If you
talk about who it is...  into the fire
I did something bad when I
was young many years ago be honest
and burned
the Melap piste and the bu that love
the smell of this truth that makes them
happy I could gymnast active good
youth it is good if you apply to your teacher
for your good deeds as a cultural heritage
title
but it is also good in form a
bad one this custom is right is very
sweet and then we will also
slowly get officials check well
it takes a while is she
a good person become for ten
million years is a bad one and
that will not change in one or two
years
slowly but steadily and also a lot of practice practice
now do it so don't become
but I am such a bad person yes
sure it was
but you improve and that is good
and this ego said the brother goes up to
pace that is
bad karma done that judge
Würzburg's monastery courtyard and this
then smokes very slowly the whole world with
thinking to do and he will
bring peace to other people because 500
people in parts rather bad karma
Burning this smoke will reach the whole
world and bring the people
desktop users before so there are
two goals number one burning meant
again two peace
and if you are tired you hear the
picture then you don't have to stay
two and a half three hours
if you feel now it is
enough go home sleep ag to the room
and slim you don't have to stay until the end
just properly merged and there are
also refreshments management has fun with
the life of the Koran man stay
the life it is hard to step
if you are in savior then you should
become the fire should be true
or 70 gladly we must the purpose and
goal of Buddhism to
become happy and therefore you should really have
fun during the ceremony
I am there for an hour to win
I have that really very exactly where SPD
as ultimately going home and watching TV
and then sleeping is good double it is
no Buddhist time not such a pedestal
okay okay we will now that the old
lamps repeat
I repeat now the euro
described is how we  They were supposed to play
in July, and in the picture there were two
friends drinking coffee together,
and that's part of this program.
The lecture is for the day before
and about glass, and after the lecture, they could
enjoy it. There were cafes with names, or
tea, and the cakes are totally
delicious here. I like them.
In the lecture, I drink the
straight angle slopes, but after the class,
I have the cake. There's more, and he
talks about what he just heard in the lecture.
Three times it hissed. That's it.
75 with his friend.
She's probably looking at the software
website. What can you remember?
In the form of Kessler, he talked about the body,
and then he also said
all the water about it.
I can't doubt it. Go
with three or four. Happy.
Why? I slept through that part, and
then your friend can tell you what
happened. About the rental car, James liked the
presentation.
I slept, that's why I
repeat. That's why
we had your visit, and 2000. That's
a 2000-year-old tradition. Drink
tea or coffee.  together and cake,
but nobody talks about complaining,
enjoy the cake and talk, class
in the east of and have fun doing it, that's
very, very important to do, so that
you have to remember it later,
that's the tradition, okay, the next
picture, yes, that's about how you
think about yourself, thinking, now
comes, are Jurassic South Foot and think that you are
sick, okay, that belongs to Signis, imagine
that you are sick,
the picture could be like when you are
inside, spiritual, Credit Suisse, said
Steve, and then thinking is very empty,
that this teaching is the medicine for you,
and all the teachers are like a doctor,
yes, the table and all the teachers together
are the medical staff, and the empty halls,
people, is the medicine,
maybe our body is not sick,
but our heart is sick all the time,
when you come here, then imagine
that the doctor,
the Turks often have to ask themselves a
question, have you taken your medicine,
yes, which, assumed
two or three times a day, I suppose,
to cure my mind,
this tradition wants, could be with
thinking that you the  I have to attend class to
get medical school, but there's
an evil spirit there, a
little doctorate & butter, the
director of the hospital in the morning, my
brother and I work for the
Buddha
Piepers Mayweathers match, it's time
and people ask me why the
teachers wear these white coats, answer
that's because it's a boxer's coat, he understands
the effect, the next one, this break, that's
because in the but in the opera, the
Elvis story,
they tell the story, they tell stories, 17 years
in the eight cinemas with pigs,
getting used to the masses, Werner Stoll, and then
they see the story, the Skipper company,
from the whirlwind, there they pull the
stories of the famous son, Peter
could once be the third man, went to my
teacher so we could go to the opera, and
then he asked why he should, or
they invited him to India, the more
for race day, there it is
where the prize, first learned,
and then my friend, he was so
funny, I don't like it,
you don't want to go to the rebreak,
that is  Not to the opera, I don't want to
hear about penises. I am, I don't want to
go to sports and watch my
mother transform 2000 years ago. I
want to be here, studying the labyrinth
and being butter, and then
they will sing about me. They will come to
disadvantages in 500 years.
It is good to respect the old sacred places,
and it is also good to read this story of the
famous saints. The nation
to dance, but every now and then, you also had to, in
principle, spend more time with
a practice, then you will have to go to the other,
and then they will make a strong grill of you. There are
the new parts in Thailand, study, yes, yes, yes, yes,
and then let some
tell you, work on the, yes, every now and then it is
also good to visit sacred places, yes,
house dog, but make his house a
sacred place, then
people will go there, house visits in 500
years.
She now has to check, she was a normal
human, then she learned the logo, Hans,
and then she had the teacher,
this was clear, and on that day
she begins to change her body, and then
she became  Buddha, and then the
people will come, and then there will be other stages at
births,
so don't waste all your time
thinking about the old brother.
You will be the next one, and they
will circle a house to be blessed. Do
you want that? And so it will be. Get
ready, change monitors.
Maybe you can even charge money for being allowed to
circle your house.
They, as a church,
that should change. If you are with your
friends
at Café Petit, then you can do that
to get the picture. It's about them
writing a song about me after I am
enlightened.
I believe you will get
the second part this afternoon, the one in which
they live.
It's not their fault, but my fault.
And who gets the new pictures this afternoon?
They want the dry version, so
you must be invited by this afternoon,
and it will be handed out to the
participants.
You can also do it with your phone. I could
n't photograph that.
I need the fogging of the
[music]. The
police officers, do
n't forget, that is lonely. The
parliamentarians, until there is
a problem nowadays.
100 years ago there was none.
Penicillin was the only way
they could operate on people
because they would have died in their own
communities due to infections. Then
they discovered penicillin, and
now when they operate,
they put penicillin in the wound,
and then you don't get infections, and
you don't die from the
pressure of the operation. Without penicillin,
you would die from Charles and the rest of the world.
But now there's a problem
in the world. Now there are people who are
resistant to penicillin.
The bacteria learn how to
fight the penicillin.
Therefore, in
some people, the bacteria in their
bodies get used to the penicillin, and
then if you give them fewer
lives, it doesn't work
anymore. Why are we talking about
Opel service? Clearly,
the reason for this class is an
accident.
The goal of this class is to eliminate
negative thoughts, and we begin a
long list of negative feelings, like a
thousand years ago. There are 48,000, and that's very
sad and depressing.
We have to make a long, long, long list
of partners.  are commentators and a
goal why come to Thailand
commission is the teachers understand because
the majority is because they are exactly and
threw these 48,000 feelings to get
when a former one shouts at you
remember pills then you remember
the stands get from me
when you can use them and then
you change your that means his children not
unhappily because they no longer have fuel space
and support from police I have been teaching for
40 years now in the summer mostly you then
with me from Toni's family and many
students accompany me setting of 20 years
and recently has always
visited me ankle I have problems with
my husband
I have problems the mass of the
wheel now goes appointment wanted she and
tells me nothing about tame 100 I have that
with great have already heard
many years ago
I need something new interest
opposite the penicillin exists and that
totally threw me off should
I help you because of the frequent
composing but you don't want me to
tell you that you the husband
Tell me something new,
he's not his thing, that's all
settled.
I gave you the nuclear bomb,
Judo Ju, and you're
not just using it, and you don't want to
celebrate afterward.
I can only give you nuclear bombs,
and prepare the catapult. You have to
buy it and then find out how we can make it
possible. New man, the husband, who exists on
his own.
You can find him at the airport. How to
fix the husband, who exists on his own. Talk to him all
evening, say
it should be me, sell it there.
I sell penicillin. Bond dissolved,
and then he won't be president. Can
live across the street here?
If we come here three or four times,
Tonio Home, and you don't eat,
practiced. When you come here, then
you can't hear it anymore.
Then you can't hear it a third time. Then
you won't
hear what I say anymore. My real
old students, or am I, when I
hold up the pen, the battle line media,
who are so fine, sleepy, immediately a home.
When you sleep, then ask your
friend to bring a pen,
the pen to tell them.  When you hear about painting,
apply it immediately because if you've heard it three
or four times, you won't be able to
do it anymore. It's a sin if the
SRG is just a great thing. Don't tell me
anything about the pen. Last year,
Justino P. Miguel succeeded. Why are
you teaching again? Because you're still arguing
with your husband.
If you stop arguing with your spouse,
then I'll stop teaching the pen.
An ice pick. The next picture is Sean
Brady as he was 100 years ago.
If he gets there exactly, then there could still be a little something. What is
he doing right now?
That was eleven years ago in 2007. At
a conference that had already been held many times, he
tried to raise money for them. Actually, he believes
that we must preserve the old books.
A lady, after you
studied that back then, you hear you have the
responsibility to keep it alive
in the world.
Sometimes you can imagine a world he's looking at. He's
across all world religions, and
Buddhism is almost extinct.
The books are almost all...
I was spared at the airport,
I think, and they sell a
tiny heart there. Huta and the team, that's
great, and
I know and I learned
calligraphy in Canada, and
then he asked me what learning is,
then I said,
may I write the diamond cutter like that?
My diamond cutter has been writing it
for 15 generations in
hip hop, and he typed the first few
letters for me, and then I said to
him, what is the meaning of
this letter, Sanogo? I don't know. So
you've been writing it for 15
generations,
yes, but we don't know what they will do
with the side shortening of the bourbon.
Keep the books alive, a tipper
- and also the meaning. There is
where we must preserve both.
Picture Keystone/AP. The books can help
disabled children, but you must keep
the meaning alive.
Then your task is to help, and you must
help with that. It's how to repay the kindness,
the kindness of someone who
ensures that the books don't
disappear.
Every generation has  This responsibility is ours;
we must preserve the books and pass them on to
the next generation.
This is your responsibility. If you were ever
here, the height of the dread after
hearing that back then, I went to the voting.
If you heard the two men in the kitchen,
then you have the
responsibility to reach the book-to-bill
Eastern European, to explain the book to the next
generation. My job is to explain it to the next
generation.
I am in the title. I will be
finished in two days, and then it's your turn.
You are the next generation.
This is your task.
Italy has Egypt. Every
generation must pass it on to the next.
Everything else falls apart.
This child has a cold,
and he's taking medicine.
He looks a little bit. He looks like this child from
other photographers. So the child is taking medicine,
but he's also sitting in Salamanca. A seat
for $100 to Porta. That's for
$100, not $400.
What is this
picture about?
[Music]
It seems really fought. It's empty,
and not the medicine. That's true,
but that's what it's about now.  Not in the picture, no,
that's not the meaning. It's
taking, it has to be.
It's about recording while I
listen. It doesn't give the child the medicine,
but brings a lot. It receives. The
answer is, does both. The concept in
the class, use the medicine. Kickl
in the class, apply the medicine. Don't
wait until you're home, you can
start using the medicine. Increasingly landed on earth.
That's something! You're sitting
next to another person for choir, and it
's cold in the class. Bösel to
sink.
Yes, among the teachers, no one can. He
teaches, then dies, but very
unpleasantly. But today, read out what
also made me cold, because Valentin could, while
the majority teach, the company
comes. The pen from the economist has a
team that would have made it so cold again.
I don't take the medicine in the
class. If the medicine is immediately, don't hold the medicine.
Second message
blow, gives the medicine, doesn't put it in
the pockets. I use it. I take it
when I'm at home. On average,
takes it right away. In the class, comes a
sound-activated air conditioning system.
No, it comes from me. Does he understand that?
Bumblebees so far have made the room so cold today.
You did it, would have taken furniture.
The medicine of the lower-class opponent,
maybe aside from the
air conditioning being switched on, has bumblebee Tim?
Who did Tim? Did the team
turn the air conditioning up too high today?
Yes, of course, why? But who did it?
You'll find it here.
When did you do that in the streets of the
bull this morning in class? They call
the medicine to drive Douglas themselves
during the class. Closed title. When
bachelors talk about the fire, that
we burn our old bad karma,
and then write on equal terms,
then worse. Start
writing on paper as bad karma thinks. Don't
say I'm not doing it alone. At
lunch, do it now, do it right away
in class,
and that's the meaning of namely
with the seven immediately. That's tradition.
Is it so busy again?
Packing, driving to the airport. Don't say
practice tomorrow morning, and should have
practiced now. Don't wait until you
belong to Doris Fitschen Mini. That's the
meaning of Paris pictures for the
next one. That's not nice. We're active from tomorrow.
Lowering is
I hope he does that, that's the
talk about them or which
title to get, that's what it's about, what
is his
motivation, a higher purpose, who
in this room, monotony, title, almost 20
teachers who really work, have been studying
for 15, 20 years,
but they have, like you, done, who
themselves, 30 years ago, came to the other, to the
other of my life,
they listen to the practitioner, get
and then they will learn, should the
ton,
it is a great honor and it is important
that you also become teachers,
that is very, very important, it should
really be, is
Dre Marica, that is my dream that you
all become teachers,
Kath,
I am ready, about computers, and here it is about,
if you are a teacher, the
Streep,
there you have to deal with three things, Formula
1 is money for the people,
it is very good to give the teacher a gift,
therefore money helps, while we
need money to buy our tickets,
about the motto, must be for the customer,
but it is not the most important title,
once from new, what does the teacher want  So,
practically speaking, that's how it's
practiced
now. It's cold when I see you like this, right now,
and he's looking over there,
where's the money
for Höppe? Then the teacher,
Michael Ernst, is happy
in the class. Records of review.
We say that's the gift of your
day, and we say it's the best
gift for Happy. If he
gives a money donation after the class, then I'm happy,
but if nothing happens, then come back to
Bali, and you say guests know each other. Since
the last long time, a house at the
fighting man. I argue much less
with my Gottesberg.
I don't expect you to be perfect.
For ten million years, you've been arguing.
The relaxed ceremony, that it won't change
in a year because otherwise, make
yourselves... Let it be sad that the
bachelor studies since his whole life,
every day, the mistake is... Let's be
honest with each other, could have to...
But if you come to me next year
and tell him... Beating and... It's slowly getting
better.
We used to... The route...
Now it's already one day a week where
we argue... Banks... And then I say...
Well done, something better, and that's
the best gift for the teacher. They get
titles, so if you're into teacher training and
Imam Ali, don't think about spending so much money on a
team. Okay,
we can also teach in a hut, and we do
n't need that big hotel in
Thailand.
If you don't have money, for
example, I taught in my car for many years
and don't expect
everyone to respect each other.
In class, they say "I love you," and at
some point, they already have big
problems.
Students are like children; we love them,
but it's true, you have difficulties, you have your shadow self.
What's going on in a
company? You can throw out the bad workers. They have
children, but a
mother can't let the earth hold her children. That's not possible, and it can't be taken away. It's
a lifelong task,
and they see that
some children, even after 16 years, have
never been in a band. Smile, but you
can't fire them. Understand,
studios with students are the same.
When you start teaching a student
in this tradition, you can't... years ago, they can't
respect them,
and then they prepare for you all day.  The
difficult part,
that's the task of a teacher.
Michael's live is clueless, there, does
n't expect that, Michael,
memory, life,
everyone is nice to smile, that's
not how it is. The task of a mother is
quite difficult,
she never sleeps, always worries,
what exactly is it like when you learn? Do
n't believe that you will, don't expect
that.
It's a lot of work but harmless, but the
mother knows that, Riedel, if you, that
is also the most beautiful task in the
whole world. The task of a mother
is the best task there is.
People drive,
I think I would like to teach.
What is your Rambourg number one is
everything, is the hardest task in
the world, number 2, over 100. I have been
taboo my whole life, is live. It is the
happiest life to have, can't do anything,
can really listen to you,
and then the second one is one of the most
difficult tasks. Kosovo's study
from Monday,
when children cause problems, the students
also do more about the praise,
but there is no better, then look,
I have done extreme more my whole life,
I  I'm extremely happy and robot, I still
have problems when I have to
raise money, please please please give
me money, one homophobia and I don't mean
then I can't sleep at night,
we have no money again and then
people ask me now, so
happy,
yes, this is the best job in the whole
world, but the motivation is very far
[Applause]
the motivation must be pure, do
n't expect that they would be ready, do
n't expect that the people, the money giver, do
n't expect 90 consists of problems,
GmbH, time, happy is, it will be, it's the
motto, there is no 23, you can see
the company behind the political, the white
building, the college is one of the red
buildings,
that would like to live here,
122, just the picture without the words in the mouth,
the 12,
I've already brought it to you, around 2, do
you have the picture, yes, 100 dollars,
I've already taught you
[Music],
different packaging, same
content, York, go
[Music],
the BND are rather, how could it become, just
country, the Germans wouldn't have
exactly, what is actually the topic
[Music],
alone when the lesson  is and if
your family is in the kitchen or
Buddhism, all the brothers will come in
the slide.
They will be checked. She's doing quite well.
They make the identical pen well.
If you are being taught, the box
must come. They are like the bees, and
you are in the high corner. Understands, it makes
them happy when you can go home. I
teach the pen for your family,
your friend,
especially if your friend argues with the
man. They are in class where the
former national will then
taste better, but much more importantly, butter
flakes. The brothers will come
because they love it when someone does
n't plug in. My old students and
tourists can. If I have the pen and
I slept, a stupid one, but I don't care. I have
as a favorite or
brothers. Come learn to sleep.
All the brothers come and listen
for the police. That's why sometimes I found.
I still need a few microphones, and
moreover, and because we are now doing questions and
answers,
yes, I have the drink.
She gets objects that go to the countries.
I said she has to go with the 100
dollars,
so they've already laid, no matter
who's in question, no matter the
topic, he decides, whoever asks,
may ask,
Hescheler
[Music]
attachments
yes,
my question is where the lesson is, we're supposed to
see everyone as butter,
but in them, it's also said that we
shouldn't surround ourselves with bad
company, what should we do
now as a student? There are two
attackers, the girlfriend is too fat, grief
and shock, there are
friends, the visitors don't, and
say, come, we can use the channel,
come, let's talk again about the content
from Thailand, to use it, which now and
already have guards, have fun doing it,
we have coffee and cake and we have
a good time together, and these are
perpetrators investigating, these were
friends back then, this is not a waste of
time and continue with the
same rank as before, money, forget it,
it will be a big movie, let's go to the cinema, there's a
new Spiderman discussion, long
on,
come, let's watch the new Spiderman,
or I watched it on TV,
really cool, I think in Shanghai they looked at
account numbers, this  Wait a minute, there
are two friends in the room
[Music]
One asked if you were going to the
country together again in the café and
the other said oh forget it let
the plenum give at this moment for
the film the second friend is like 1 de
tomorrow the second woman to him
you should say thank you I like going into the opposite outside
maybe tomorrow has of course
also said we have to people and also
Keller wants the new party but today
fear but today I would like to
repeat
the service is the second person a
Buddha yes sure why testing the
premature babies
who grabbed you okay the check-in who
check if you are a good student
this week a Buddha is coming so
maybe there is your husband and he
writes
and it is a butter that is over Pentecost
but what you have learned
he is taught and learned don't believe
that all brothers net
you learn from his problems more
the people who really give you
difficulties who teach
when we have no problems then
we don't think of the teachers when we
have difficulties and problems
then we remember the  Labels
troublemaker is so easy that this
type of trouble with his
mother dogs and maybe but also
not as a reward
we don't know could be
that it's acute but also the money
was but it's helpful for us if
we think that it is or is he
smiled booth is is the husband who
yells at you a Buddha I don't know
so is it possible if they have a baby you
camping construction costs would they then
yell at you so that you to the teacher
is yes that is possible
the car and that's logical
you don't have to say
the blow set yesterday said
my husband is a brother is dead yes
that's true but on the level on which
we can move we can honestly
say it could be a borderline citizen
judis break
my mother would be and is not paying any respect
then you would really collect badly
I'll tell a story I
worked in diamond business for 19 years at
the beginning of the encounter communication
workers at the beginning I also
worked otherwise because the company couldn't afford the
salary  We couldn't
pay anyone
[music]
and then they didn't ask if it's
okay if we pay you next week.
I said yes. We didn't have any
money. Can you do it next week?
And I think they... I had a
relationship with them for six weeks, and later, with that,
we became the biggest sinners. We were
the biggest diamond company in the world,
and I had an extremely high pace, and
then I took half of my salary
directly to the monastery at lunchtime without
taxes, legally.
And they took half of my salary,
and every six months I was
at my boss's,
so he still owed me 100 or 200
thousand dollars.
And today you have to write the check for the
monastery. Movement of the USA...
How many was it again?
I said 200,000, we'll take it, and then I
said okay, let's make it 300,000.
He added hundreds of thousands more. It will be
a monastery,
and he did that for many years, and
finally, that gave an extremely large
additional amount.
Ask a personal question. They
are all...  Jews,
you're an Israeli, SPD is top, and those
are really great characters. View, do
you seem like a manipulative, a federal, for months? Why do
you give more extra money for the
festival every time? There's really a
big portion extra on top of that. Why do
you do that? You never know which
religion is right.
Okay,
Kosovo sneaks through.
Maybe you Jews are right, where the team is. Maybe
the Christians have it hard. Are
the Muslims right? House bonus mode of
ski. Maybe a monastery is right.
So in person, fit. So if you're
intelligent, donate those, I'm totally
next to blood red, then you'll be in
a good place. It's really funny. Advertising
film and sketches, just like boogie-
woogie, the difficulties make.
We don't know who a brother is. It
waved babies. Point check
better. There are so many religions,
maybe, and also someone to
respect who isn't Buddhist. It's a
problem. If you believe that someone
is a brother and respect him, you
still make good seed even if you later
find out that he has to. It
is certainly just as much respect the
mouse.  as well as safe is long every
organization to donate
[Applause]
[Music]
gesche lotto sachsen stift the café
teach come all butter to
watch us is it because we the
things producers of compo there where the side
or from the other side
good question this is the second chapter
this chapter is called arising and
passing away when my brother comes was
there I have to ask them then to
come
winter brotherly struggle countries brother comes
now comes then comes there from you there are
two different kinds of
arising the Buddha won but he
comes when we
I'll give you an example to hurry - mother
I live in a small town in the town hall the
robot very very small
town in the channel in China New York is it
modern is New York a small town is
my guy but the city where
I live is super glide 2000 I
think there are 3000 people who
live there and we have a post
the tool this works and
two women work there  new videos I think they
're 19 now
and if you write a letter and give it to
him you have to ring the bell first
we as engine I think they
sleep in the back room lid will take
care of
then they come in
and how is it behind Klose 20
posts
I need 15 minutes to get to the post office if
I'm allowed to write a letter Markus
Meik and is at the old lady in the
post office and takes it to myself
analyzed
then it will take two weeks so far
more delivered
I can there in 15 minutes in
Saxony
so let's say write to Gesche
Michael would you Bellier search so
you'll be really totally stupid and I would have
him and give it to the old lady Tutu
is after two weeks the
postman youngest company I believe it's
the old woman's son then he gives
the envelope to the eyes and then
I open the envelope from Gesche performs there is
still a question should
I now over the Rio carrier
orders the letter brought no he did
n't have the letter
he still has the letter  delivered and
his husband is again postman
Europe always you wrote the letter
because he had he puts in Europe for
you if your husband argues with the
DICOM in July us then he brings you his
own seed loved could help
if someone criticizes or who
wrote the letter and
wrote and then she does
n't bring the image carrier and he has nothing
always cheering he is not to blame for
it only had his own Bremen
if someone I kick her do it then
he is only the postman
he didn't write the letter
you wrote the letter understand
why no one talks about it now so
some people ask me
[Music]
for example if I take an aspirin
I have a headache and taking aspirin does it
work or not during the day
sometimes catch the authority
if you have helped other people in the past
if she
has headphones
if you have the tame that they bring me
the film to me then the medicine is with you
if you have ignored it because your
friends' head always then if you
take the aspirin it won't work and with yoga
it's exactly from senior bought  One goes
with yoga and will really start like
elsewhere, of course, and one
goes here to the same class, they hurt themselves in the process.
Glass is the post, the class is again
postman's ministerial post.
Aspirin is the postman, they did
n't write the letter. It says
annual meeting in slippers. So if
you're in the cafe and explaining the pen to your friend
and the Buddhas come and
the Potters come to you, the
Potters come to you,
never forget the three questions: Do I have
a pen in my hand? Number two,
what is number two? Do I have a pen in my
hand that I create? Yes, number three,
he could. Do I have a pen in my
hand that comes from the pen? If you have the
pen in the cafe, the brothers will come. Yes,
they come because the seed
for it will be a Buddha. If he
explains the pen that you didn't make,
no, Google.com,
but comes from or to dark jerseys. So
never forget the same question. This
energy giant plans then that you should never
be confused. Is their ability a
substance in my hand? Year is
the  Compromise is a pen in my
hand that I create. Yahoo belongs to
computers. Does the pen in my hand come
from the pen? No, is the brother? Could
Djokovic be back? Is there in the
coffee shop? Because not from his seeds.
Come
yesterday. And the topic is the eight
impossible scanners.
That means it can't be. That's
not from a server. Cuddles. Another
question.
[Music]
I just wanted to clarify the question because the
seeds create our world.
So the world is created by our seeds.
But how can it be that I play to a
bulldozer? How do we do that?
People assumed that I was an
example for them. I wasn't
born a Buddhist. I was
raised Christian.
We were four brothers. Back and my
mother took us to church. Allen
Johnson and I really
enjoyed church and it was very
nice. I always go to China now
and then. Still go to my
old church that I also went to as a child.
I know how much I like
the feeling very much. The prayer  It reminds me a lot of the
museum nine times when my mother
went with us to church and she
said please we do it like this in
Buddhism cross your legs here coast even
as a small child and
then she said do your hands
then we were hands
Lausanne said close your eyes
close your eyes and think about
in this world think about everyone in this
world I am that
are so funny because they
think everything is clear to the mother and that is difficult
in short meet pray for all people
try a fat builder think about
animals to help and we try that
we lied so much and sometimes
we parents the children believe everything they
can become members to come up
when you get older you do you in
life there I can't
help all people in the world is only at
pleasant 1000 for the applause
need Oslo
I'll give you a few minutes
I was trained in this because one was
rebuilt by my mother so that I
at least think about all people and
stand by them or even 30 20
that's not possible it's okay
for the  Small ones go,
but when you get older, well, it's never been true, it's just not possible
that I
can change the whole world. One
person can't change the whole world. To
get
and then you don't believe anymore, that's why I
told a story about Norway, it has
no coast. Last year, Christian was
here, lots of luxury. Before, he looks like a fool.
I hate that guy, extreme. He's totally
good-looking, blond, long, and
muscular, and besides, he's already from the
richest family. They have to
listen, so there are three reasons why
I'm so annoyed.
He's hard, and number three is extremely
rich. Both before, but the horse, the
worst thing about an extreme and
double top service, and that's really
difficult. I'm jealous of him, but I can do it.
So, in the exam, I have a boy
and a young guy from their class, the Sortimo.
I always wanted to have a girlfriend,
and to kiss me, I want
someone to know me. Crystal, you know, sure, I
'm here, and now I know what I have to do.
What are these films? Must be in Oslo. There's
a landlord of the restaurant La Hypo.
Customers, many people who would have that
today I will go to the restaurant,
I will every woman in the restaurant is
but wants to, and with that I plant the chassis, it
is to find a girlfriend who is
not applicable,
the women also have that, it doesn't work that way,
what should I do then if you
want a partner, June had to tame it for that,
if you want to plant a tooth,
you have to find lonely people, should be allowed
to sit,
I suggest to you what others do the way you
go, that a Jew pays and you are looking for
an old lady, once a week
Roubini holds, you go to the cinema with her,
she says no, listen, suspect, we have to,
maybe she has no family
left that she can visit, and with that
you can use the name Mimi, allowed to be his
girlfriend, his wife, that's when
I came, hot rhythms, and six
weeks later I got an email from
him, it
worked, I went out with the
old lady
to the cinema, planned as a ninth together,
and I don't now, I like that, are you
finished, exactly six times six
months later I got a second
email from them, and
here and there there was a  In the video, we turn
the tree towards...  - The video lasts about
two minutes.
Winter is possible in euros. The video
is on...
I don't know what's being said.
Cinema, cinema, the 19th
cinema, cinema, that's cinema. Going to the cinema, cinema, cinema,
gladly mobile, and that means
going to the cinema. My ex-husband... Six
months after he met his girlfriend,
he sent me this video,
and he tells me that movement...
What is the video? Going... Ready... Okay, here we go.
Dollar Aquino seawater, how
activities set...
[Music]
Putsilo ca
as cappuccino. That's not China. I
can... Pacino or long...
No shot...
[Music]
[Music] [
Applause]
The video player...
This video is shown on television in Norway every week.
Video US paid for
international telephone co. And the video
was financed by the national
telephone company and the government
is very good. And at the end, it says that
if a young man goes to the cinema with an old man,
people become victims of physical... I
only get tickets by boat. Then
the parts will be that the telephone company and the...  The
government will pay for the tickets
[applause]
but Christian is and now the
big question is how did that go with the dinosaurs? There are
everywhere in Beijing,
over 200,000 young
people from our town went to the cinema for hundreds of thousands of
seniors. Everyone there, how did it start?
The new dictionary is the guy who
decided not to kiss all the women in the
restaurant.
It started with him. A
person,
he met his girlfriend,
especially in Southern Europe. Now, for about five
years, he had no girlfriend. How
come you have one now? What did
you do?
You go to the salsa and then our
friend of friends, 565 friend of enemy of friend,
there, four steps. The virus spread
in Norway from the Rhine,
starting from a crystal ball.
So there are two types. All people
on the island,
you can with a mother in the church. I want
all people to do that. You are
good.
It doesn't help people directly, but
indirectly it is very, very good. Or apply
the step closer to commentary
then.  Will you become financially independent and
therefore rich? You were healthy and have
office space.
You have a wonderful relationship with
a happy marriage.
New York pop and then your
girlfriend will be there and welcome here and the
friends of friends will want to
come and the friends of friends
of friends will go
and then the government makes a movie
and you might be the one there, understand
your roof over brush youth. You do the best
you can to
help every person. You knew how to apply
the four steps yourself. Farmer
news. You have to be successful.
Come to the office. Then the people will be there
with their speedboat. But it is possible to make
the whole world bright. This person per
so Paul.
Every person has this made it possible. What do you have to do? You have to. You have that.
You have
a happy marriage. You are living a healthy
life.
You are really young. You mean you are
a human billboard. Kohl. Thank you.
[Applause] [
Music]